I just picked these three tomatoes from my tomato tree.
Now listen, I know that it's like big freaking Wolf Amanda is three tomatoes.
However, this is really important to me because I have really spent the last two years changing my life
and becoming decolonized not just intellectually but also in how I am relating to the land
and to the power of this earth and to the power of our energy as it connects to this earth.
And so being able to actually like grow something and eat it is not just simply like a flex of green summery
but it really is the root of, pun intended, our ability to create actual sovereignty from this system
that has continued to function to undermine our connection to everything.
So as I hold these tomatoes, I want to remind y'all that every second Wednesday of the month
you can catch me in Harlem at Comedy in Harlem on 147th and St. Nick with Radical Rhythms Experience
which is my combination of music, comedy, and energy work.
I don't know where else you're going to find something like that but baby, I'm bringing it to you
because I truly believe that us understanding energy work that has been practiced by ancients,
by indigenous folks for centuries is imperative in our understanding how to overthrow the powers that be
that continue to disempower us.
So get your tickets at comedyinharlem.com and if you're not able to make it,
you'll be able to watch online at YouTube AmandaSeal TV.
Get your energy right.
Come and join me, Amanda Seals, this Wednesday, August 12th
and every second Wednesday at Comedy in Harlem for Radical Rhythms Experience.
Every month we come together to level up our vibration with music, humor, and each other.
Tickets available at comedyinharlem.com.
...